Welcome to Kolo 2026.0.
In this version, we will once again enhance your digital experience and efficiency through a series of new functions.
First is the new integrated function.
In addition to the conventional sewing, you can now connect the panels using the integrated tool.
The software provides three flexible operating methods.
Fast integration is used for the integration of internal patterns and panels.
Brush integration is convenient for you to smear a specific area of ​​integration.
Fill-in integration can be realized quickly.
The complete panel is integrated into another panel.
This update will enhance the accuracy of the production accuracy of sportswear, outdoor clothing and shoes.
In terms of creative expression,
The 3D virtual model line sketching process,
Has become more efficient.
You can now directly hook the draft on the model,
And convert these drafts directly into panels.
After completing the draft drawing,
Convert to 3D brush to continue editing and adjusting.
Or you can also flatten the draft into panels.
The system will automatically arrange and sew,
Let inspiration quickly become a real clothing structure.
Then there is the automatic tie-dye string function.
Now you can quickly add a belt effect to the clothing or bag belt.
The operation is very intuitive.
You can not only easily complete a complex string path,
You can also create a corresponding strap version.
And edit and adjust at any time according to design needs.
The hardware picture has also been upgraded.
When checking the distribution of hardware,
You can freely switch between universal and fabric modes.
When choosing the universal mode,
No matter what kind of fabric is used,
As long as the value should reach 120% or higher,
The area will be displayed in red.
And after switching to the fabric mode,
The color range will be customized according to the physical properties of the fabric.
This can help you scientifically evaluate the harmony of clothing according to different fabric properties.
We have made many updates to the version generator.
As usual,
You can enter the CSV file or enter the value directly.
Quickly and easily add the measurement value.
Now you can also directly enter the code information.
You only need to add the code specifications.
Then pass the code rules.
Or directly enter the measurement value of each size to complete.
The measurement value of each size can be entered.
After generating the version,
The system will automatically arrange the version and sew it on the model.
At the same time,
All measurement points will automatically be applied to the measurement point option card of the object window.
If you set the code,
The relevant specifications will be synchronized.
As long as the version is created using the version generator,
You can return the tool to continue editing at any time.
Or you can also directly use the measurement point tool in the 2D window to modify the measurement value.
Our measurement point calculator function can help you.
For measurement points,
Do a variety of combination calculations.
You only need to click on the calculator icon.
Add the required measurement point value to the calculator.
You can carry out basic mathematical operation.
You can choose to store these mathematical formulas in the computing department.
So that it is easy to check.
You can see the calculation results in different size numbers.
And can apply these newly generated mathematical images to the item window measurement point list.
In addition, in the attribute editor,
You can also check the measurement point at any time.
All the calculations involved.
In this update,
You can lock the custom measurement on the map or on the outside of the version.
You can also create a custom measurement point within the map.
And accurately set the starting location in the attribute editor.
Achieve accurate map positioning.
In Clo 2026.0,
Appliance irregular numbers becomes more efficient.
Now you just need to press the Shift key.
You can select multiple unit格 and multiply to modify the value at the same time.
And it will not affect other size numbers.
Under the arrangement settings,
You can now choose the same clothes and the same image.
This ensures that all the versions of the same clothes are in the same direction.
When your arrangement task involves multiple direction of killing,
This function will be very useful.
Clo 2026.0 adds a new isolation selection to check the options.
It will automatically hide all unselected parts.
This makes it easier for you to observe the interior of the clothes.
Or from the point of view that is usually difficult to observe and operate.
Finely adjust.
We have improved the rendering function of the style map.
Now support the measurement point and the sticker while rendering the style map.
You can not only see these measurement points directly.
You can also use the measurement point selection card of the object window.
You can choose the specific measurement value you want to display.
And directly adjust the size in the window of the style map.
For the hair performance, we have also improved the depth.
Now when you apply the sticker to the hair material.
The system will automatically generate a cover and remove the hair in the area.
Ensure that the sticker can be clearly displayed.
In addition, you can also use the edit sewing tool.
To define the hair effect of the seam area.
Accurate control of the hair thickness near the seam line.
To determine the visibility of the seam area.
In order to continue to provide an optimized experience for Closet users.
We redesigned the content page and workroom interface in Closet.
When 3D files are uploaded to Closet.
The first page the user sees is the cover part.
You can fill in the main information through the text below.
For example, the category.
Click on the settings button in the upper right corner.
You can define the content displayed in the first page.
You can check the details in the purple label page on the right.
For example, details, file version and link content.
The next part is the viewfinder.
We have made many improvements to the 3D viewfinder.
Including the first option on the switch bar.
Users can now use the Closet high-quality rendering in the 3D viewfinder.
Click on it.
Click on the label page in the upper right corner.
Users can check the label and color labels separately.
Click on the tool bar on the left.
Users can manage the version of the upload.
The next one is the BOM material list.
It will display the corresponding material list according to the settings in Closet.
Users can also add blank lines to fill in.
New material information created in the Closet software before upload.
Click on each part of the material list table.
Edit each material data.
Next to the material list is the POM measurement point part.
Similar to the previous one, it will display the measurement point data according to the settings in Closet.
In the attached part.
Users can upload other relevant articles.
The final content analysis will show the creation period of the model.
Users can click on the button in the upper right corner to share and comment.
Users can also check the activity date next to the comment.
Finally, users can click on the personal image icon.
Change the theme to dark mode.
If users return to the workstation level.
You can click on the button in the style corner to preview relevant information.
Through the above updates.
Users can enjoy a more smooth collaboration experience in the design development process.
Thank you for watching.
To learn more about the new features and updates of Closet 2026.0.
Please visit our official website clo3d.com.